Finding Aid for Jennifer Granholm papers, 1992-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Communications Division
  - Director’s Files (Liz Boyd)
    - News Clippings
      - Balanced budget avoids huge cuts 2003 (Box 186)
      - Balanced Cuts 2003 (Box 186)
      - Governor keeps tax vow -- sort of 2003 (Box 186)
      - MEAP Award to go from $2,500 to $500 2003 (Box 186)
      - Granholm cuts and keeps promises 2003 (Box 186)
      - Granholm displays mettle over 100 days 2003 (Box 186)
      - Granholm wants action to combat lead poisoning 2003 (Box 186)
      - Granholm vows to fix state’s 216 failing schools 2003 (Box 186)
      - Granholm giving tourism a lift 2003 (Box 186)
      - Gays applaud governor’s attitude 2003 (Box 186)
      - Granholm plans fund for schools 2003 (Box 186)
      - Granholm promises help for torn city 2003 (Box 186)
      - Disabled can earn more and keep benefits 2003 (Box 186)
      - Crackdown for kids 2003 (Box 186)
      - Deal buoys Detroit Medical Center (DMC), schools 2003 (Box 186)
      - Record budget shortfalls 2003 (Box 186)
      - State Budget Compromise Prudent and Fair 2003 (Box 186)
      - Budget boosts Granholm’s status 2003 (Box 186)
      - Budget Pain and Relief 2003 (Box 186)
      - Covering deficit turns personal 2003 (Box 186)
      - 1,000 jobs at Detroit Medical Center (DMC) spared 2003 (Box 186)
      - Detroit Medical Center (DMC) to adopt auditing change 2003 (Box 186)
      - Granholm vows to fix mental health system 2003 (Box 186)
      - Governor to veto cuts to schools 2003 (Box 186)
      - Book Joy 2003 (Box 186)
      - Detroit Medical Center (DMC) officials face questions on emergency funds 2003 (Box 186)
      - Governor gets an earful on the issues 2003 (Box 186)
      - Granholm pursues gasoline gougers 2003 (Box 186)
      - Granholm’s plan: Help at-risk kids 2003 (Box 186)
      - School aid fund May get $98 million 2003 (Box 186)
      - Budget cuts see sensible as explained undated (Box 186)
      - Attorney General Race 2002 (Box 187)
      - Gubernatorial Campaign 2002, 2 folders (Box 187)
      - Legislature 2002 (Box 187)
      - Post-Election Clips 2002 (Box 187)
      - Taxes circa 2002 (Box 187)
      - Miscellaneous 2000, 2 folders (Box 187)
    - Speeches
      - 2002
        - Win -- Victory Speech (Box 187)
      - 2003
        - Central Middle School Sweet Success Program (Box 187)
        - Select a Taste of Michigan (Box 187)
        - Michigan Life Sciences Corridor (Box 187)
        - MI-Cops -- Michigan State Police Memorial (Box 187)
        - Water Board (Box 187)
        - Testimony before the U. S. House of Representatives Subcommittee on Highways, Transit & Pipelines, Committee on Transportation & Infrastructure (Box 187)
        - Employee Voicemail Recognition Message (Box 187)
        - Wood Radio (Box 187)
        - Public Service Announcement Scripts (Box 187)
        - Principals Academy Opening (Box 187)
        - Brown v. Board of Education 49th Anniversary (Box 187)
        - Emily’s List Annual Luncheon (Box 187)
        - DCX/UP Fuel Cell Announcement (Box 187)
        - Aretha Franklin (Box 187)
        - State of the State (Box 187)
        - Leading Poisoning in Children (Box 187)
        - 21st Century Community Learning Center Grants (Box 187)
        - 3rd Annual Martin Luther King, Jr. Tribute Breakfast Optimist club Foundation of Central Detroit (Box 187)
        - Acceptance Remarks, Robert L. Millender Award -- SCLC Minister’s Awards Dinner (Box 187)
        - Justice James Brickley Portrait Ceremony, Hall of Justice, Supreme Court Chambers (Box 187)
        - 21st Century Community Learning Center Grants (Box 187)
        - Michigan Collaborative Early Childhood Conference (MCECC) (Box 187)
        - MASA Midwinter Conference Amway Grand Plaza Hotel (Box 187)
        - HOPE Scholarship Program, Don Johnson Field House (Box 187)
        - Child Development Conference (Box 187)
        - United Auto Workers (UAW) National CAP Conference, Michigan Delegation (Box 187)
        - United Auto Workers (UAW) Women’s Event (Box 187)
        - Small Business & Technology Development Center Announcement, DeVos Campus (Box 187)
        - Grand Rapids Chamber of Commerce Annual Meeting (Box 187)
        - Legacy Associates Foundation -- 6th Annual Scholarship Dinner (Box 187)
        - Auto Alliance Announcement (Box 187)
        - Michigan Association of Counties (Box 187)
        - Global Engine Alliance Announcement, DaimlerChrysler Headquarters (Box 187)
        - Michigan Legislative Black Caucus -- Black History Month Program (Box 187)
        - Michigan Democratic Party (MDP) Spring Statewide Convention (Box 187)
        - Michigan Association of Broadcasters (Box 187)
        - Michigan State Building and Construction Trades Council Legislative Conference (Box 187)
        - SAE Reception (Box 187)
        - Covering the Uninsured (Box 187)
        - ArtServe “Arts Alive Daily” (Box 187)
        - Michigan Catholic Conference Building Dedication (Box 187)
        - Land Use Council Meeting (Box 187)
        - Michigan Municipal League (Box 187)
        - State Board of Education (Box 187)
        - Michigan Association for the Education of Young Children (MIAEYC) Annual Conference (Box 187)
        - Blues PAC -- Blue Cross Blue Shield (BCBS) of Michigan Headquarters (Box 187)
        - University of Michigan Commencement (Box 187)
        - Opening Ceremony of Grayling Elementary School’s Reading Center (Box 187)
        - Michigan Prisoner ReEntry Initiative (Box 187)
        - Michigan State University Center for Urban Affairs Article (Box 187)
        - Coalition on Temporary Shelter (Box 187)
        - Michigan Life Sciences Corridor Conference (Box 187)
        - Michigan Township Association Capitol Conference (Box 187)
        - Michigan National Guard Deployment (Box 187)
        - AFL-CIO Civil Rights Award (Box 187)
        - Crime Victims’ Rights Week Vigil (Box 187)
        - Reverend Kenneth Flowers -- 25th Anniversary of Preaching Banquet, St. John’s Armenian Church (Box 187)
        - Arab Community Center for Economic and Social Services (ACCESS) Anniversary Banquet (Box 187)
        - Community Coalition -- Black Slate and East Side Slate, Roostertail Supper Club 100 (Box 187)
        - Hospice of Michigan -- 18th Annual Crystal Rose Ball (Box 187)
        - AFL-CIO Annual Statewide Conference (Box 187)
        - Michigan National Guard Deployment (Box 187)
        - Global Engine Alliance Celebration, Dundee Community Schools Building (Box 187)
        - David Alan Groner Investiture, Congregation Shaarey Zedek (Box 187)
        - Don’t Trash Michigan Kick-Off, UFCW Hall (Box 187)
        - Michigan Jewish Conference/State of Michigan Holocaust Commemoration (Box 187)
        - Teamsters Legislative Conference (Box 187)
        - 22nd Annual Conference of the Michigan Coalition for Human Rights (Box 187)
        - MFT&SRP (Teachers’ Union) -- 67th Annual Convention (Box 187)
        - Michigan State University Commencement (Box 187)
        - Jewish Theological Seminary Annual Gala Dinner, Congregation Shaarey Zedek (Box 187)
        - Michigan Democratic Party (MDP) Jefferson Jackson Dinner (Box 187)
        - Principals Academy Opening Session (Box 187)
        - Grantmakers/Grantseekers Conference (Box 187)
        - Michigan Jewish Community Council of Metropolitan Detroit (Box 187)
        - First Fugitive Sweep, Executive Plaza (Box 187)
        - Designing Healthy Livable Communities Conference (Box 187)
        - Mercy High School Commencement (Box 187)
        - Campus Martius (Box 187)
        - Travel Michigan Tour (Box 187)
        - William C. Sterling State Park Rededication (Box 187)
        - Venture Capitalist Remarks, Michigan Growth Capital Symposium (Box 187)
        - House Democratic Caucus, House Caucus Chambers (Box 187)
        - Speech to Hispanic Chamber of Commerce (Box 187)
        - Remarks at GM Technical Center (Box 187)
        - Lansing Economic Club Talking Points (Box 187)
        - Benton Harbor Visit (Box 187)
        - Talking Points; Site Consultants Event (Box 187)
        - Talking Points; Second Fugitive Felon Sweep (Box 187)
        - Pfizer Press Conference, Southwest Michigan Innovation Center (Box 187)
        - Talking Points; “Freedom to Work” Bill Signing (Box 187)
        - Funeral Service Remarks for State Trooper Kevin Marshall, St. Anne Catholic Church (Box 187)
        - TechNet Teleconference (Box 187)
        - Detroit Medical Center (DMC) Press Conference (Box 187)
        - Small Group Market Reform Signing, Canada Dry Bottling Company (Box 187)
        - Talking Points; Detroit Renaissance Press Conference, Compuware Headquarters (Box 187)
        - Dedication for New CMS Energy Headquarters (Box 187)
        - Acceptance of “Granholm Challenge,” MOTT Community College Regional Technology Center (RTC) (Box 187)
        - Prosecuting Attorneys Association of Michigan (Box 187)
        - Center for Automotive Research, Management Briefing (Box 187)
        - Talking Points, Flint Faith Community Briefing -- Mott Community College (Box 187)
        - Road Project Resumption and Enhancement Grant Check (Box 187)
        - Great Lakes Regional Training Center (Box 187)
        - Michigan Army National Guard/Air National Guard Annual Review and Memorial Service (Box 187)
        - Governor’s Luncheon and Reception at Michigan State Fairgrounds (Box 187)
        - Benton Harbor High School Visit (Box 187)
        - Lake Michigan College Luncheon (Box 187)
        - MSHDA Ground Breaking Event (Box 187)
        - Remarks; Mackinac Bridge Walk (Box 187)
        - Vision for Urban Redevelopment -- Motor City Blight Busters Fundraiser (Box 187)
        - Michigan Works! -- Extension of Unemployment Insurance Benefits (Box 187)
        - MCRC 40th Anniversary Dinner (Box 187)
        - Laborfest (Box 187)
        - Consular Corps Reception (Box 187)
        - Michigan Economic Development Corporation (MEDC) CEO Announcement (Box 187)
        - The Civics Institute First Annual Celebration of Civic Engagement (Box 187)
        - Governor’s University Summit (Box 187)
        - Arab American and Chaldean Council (Box 187)
        - United States Arab Economic Summit (Box 187)
        - Early Child Summit (Box 187)
        - Hispanic Heritage Month (Box 187)
        - Michigan Tourism Keynote Luncheon Speaker (Box 187)
        - Opening Ceremony for Max M. Fisher Music Center (Box 187)
        - Project Rehab 35th Anniversary, Fredrick Meijer Gardens (Box 187)
        - AFSCME Council 25, 14th Constitutional Convention (Box 187)
        - AFL-CIO Cope Dinner (Box 187)
        - Annual Focus: HOPE Walk (Box 187)
        - Michigan Sheriff’s Association Fall Conference (Box 187)
        - Kick-off of Coastal Campaign (Arcadia) (Box 187)
        - Women’s Day Celebration, Mayflower Congregational United Church (Box 187)
        - 6th Grade Laptop Rollout (Box 187)
        - Early Education Town Hall (Box 187)
        - Introduction of Her Majesty Queen Rania Al-Abdullah of Jordan (Box 187)
        - State Bar of Michigan President’s Dinner (Box 187)
        - Habitat for Humanity, Second Ebenezer Baptist Church (Box 187)
        - “Michigan Matters,” at Delphi Steering Systems (Box 187)
        - “Michigan Matters,” at Irwin Seating Systems (Box 187)
        - Stakeholder Meeting (Box 187)
        - Cool Cities Advisory Panel (Box 187)
        - First Land Use Executive Directive (Box 187)
        - Council of Michigan Foundations (Box 187)
        - ArtServe Michigan -- 10th Annual Governor’s Awards for Art and Culture (Box 188)
        - Michigan Education Association (MEA) Fall Representative Assembly (Box 188)
        - Opening of Regionalism Conference (Box 188)
        - National Governors Association (NGA) Quality Preschool Forum Opening Remarks (Box 188)
        - Instructional Excellence Conference (Box 188)
        - Wayne State University Commencement, Receiving Honorary Law Degree (Box 188)
        - Council of Baptist Pastors of Detroit and Vicinity (Box 188)
        - Cool Cities Summit (Box 188)
        - Transportation Summit (Box 188)
        - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce (Box 188)
        - Attorney General/ Family Independence Agency (FIA) Child Support Agreement (Box 188)
        - Detroit Renaissance (Box 188)
        - Michigan Education Association (MEA) Summer Leadership Conference Telephone Interview (Box 188)
        - Lead Press Conferences, Saginaw/Detroit (Box 188)
        - Biosciences Research and Commercialization Center at Western Michigan University (Box 188)
        - U.S. -- Japan Association Conference (Box 188)
        - Arab American and Chaldean Council (Box 188)
        - Regional Faith-Based Reception (Box 188)
        - Opening of Regionalism Conference (Box 188)
        - Yeshiva Beth Yehuda (Box 188)
        - Job Creation (Box 188)
      - 2004
        - North American Auto Show Tour (Box 188)
        - 16th North American International Auto Show, Charity Preview (Box 188)
        - Family Independence Agency (FIA) Directors Meeting (Box 188)
        - 125th Anniversary of Capitol (Box 188)
        - Detroit Renaissance Board Meeting (Box 188)
        - Thank Your Mentor Press Conference -- First Gentleman Dan Mulhern (Box 188)
        - House Democratic Caucus Retreat (Box 188)
        - Thank Your Mentor, National Mentoring Month (Box 188)
        - Annual Martin Luther King, Jr. Unity Breakfast (Box 188)
        - Michigan Quarter Unveiling (Box 188)
        - Third Share Health Care Event (Box 188)
        - Michigan Association of School Administrators (Box 188)
        - Michigan Press Association -- Winter Convention (Box 188)
        - Service Employees International Union (SEIU) Local 79 Steward Conference (Box 188)
        - Breakfast for Mental Health Commission (Box 188)
        - Michigan Society of Association Executive (Box 188)
        - Saginaw Economic Forum (Box 188)
        - Economic Club of Grand Rapids (Box 188)
        - Global Engine Alliance II Announcement (Box 188)
        - Prayer Brunch Speech (Box 188)
        - Cornerstone Alliance Annual Meeting (Box 188)
        - Annual Black History Program -- Michigan Legislative Black Caucus (Box 188)
        - Michigan Concrete Paving Association Workshop (Box 188)
        - Michigan State Building & Construction Trades Council Legislative Conference (Box 188)
        - Water Legacy Act Press Conference (Box 188)
        - Delphi Corporation Annual Automotive Matchmaker Conference & Ribbon Cutting Lansing Convention Center (Box 188)
        - Michigan Association of Broadcasters (Box 188)
        - General Motors Delta Township Assembly Plant Construction Ceremony (Box 188)
        - Cherry Commission (Box 188)
        - Dedication of the Radiology Oncology Center, Mount Clemens General Hospital (Box 188)
        - Pennsylvania Manufacturing Summit (Box 188)
        - Economic Club of Lapeer (Box 188)
        - Bill Signing Ceremony for Trash Package (Box 188)
        - Kerry Introduction -- Wayne State University Economic Speech (Box 188)
        - Capitol Area Cesar Chavez Event -- A Day to Remember (Box 188)
        - 27th Annual Governor’s Breakfast (Box 188)
        - Hyundai America Technical Center Groundbreaking (Box 188)
        - Federal Bar Association Luncheon (Box 188)
        - Early Childhood Forum for Grantmakers and Policymakers (Box 188)
        - NAACP Freedom Fund Dinner (Box 188)
        - Credit Scoring Ban (Box 188)
        - Alper/Katz Wedding (Box 188)
        - Manufacturing Roundtable (Box 188)
        - Base Closure and Realignment Commission (BRAC) Task Force Press Conference (Box 188)
        - BioMed Expo (Box 188)
        - Teamster’s Delegate Meeting (Box 188)
        - Employee Recognition Event (Box 188)
        - Employee Recognition Event (Box 188)
        - Vision 2020 4th Annual Town Hall Meeting (Box 188)
        - Holland Tulip Time Governor’s Luncheon (Box 188)
        - Montcalm Community College Commencement (Box 188)
        - Trial Lawyer Banquet (Box 188)
        - Arab Community Center for Economic and Social Services (ACCESS) 33rd Annual Anniversary Banquet (Box 188)
        - Michigan Department of Transportation (MDOT) Funds Announced (Box 188)
        - Investiture Ceremony for Mark Smith (Box 188)
        - Lead Screening Bill Signing (Box 188)
        - Legislative Black Caucus, 50th Anniversary of Brown v. Board of Education (Box 188)
        - Michigan Week Kick-off (Box 188)
        - Oral Testimony to the Committee on Energy and Commerce -- House of Representatives (Box 188)
        - Testimony to Subcommittee on Highways, Transit and Pipelines Transportation Committee, House of Representatives (Box 188)
        - Press Conference on Homeland Security Funding with Senator Stabenow (Box 188)
        - No Child Left Behind (NCLB) Conference (Box 188)
        - University of Michigan Flint/Bank One Women’s Business Conference (Box 188)
        - James M. Pelton Firefighters Memorial Highway Dedication (Box 188)
        - Millie Jeffrey Remarks (Box 188)
        - May 15th Luncheon Notes (Box 188)
        - Women’s Day Program at Foss Avenue Baptists Church (Box 188)
        - Kellogg Michigan Economic Growth Authority (MEGA) Announcement (Box 188)
        - Lansing Michigan Economic Growth Authority (MEGA) Announcement (Box 188)
        - Southeast Michigan Economic Growth Authority (MEGA) Announcement (Box 188)
        - Travel Tour Press Conference (Box 188)
        - Rouge Industries/Severstal Reception (Box 188)
        - Michigan Credit Union League Annual Convention (Box 188)
        - Tri-Centennial State Park Dedication (Box 188)
        - Michigan Community Service Commission -- Governor’s Service Awards (Box 188)
        - Kalamazoo Rotary (Box 188)
        - Detroit Women’s Economic Club (Box 188)
        - German American Chamber of Commerce (Box 188)
        - Benton Harbor -- Progress Since Summer (Box 188)
        - Mackinac Conference Opening Remarks (Box 188)
        - Lake St. Clair (Box 188)
        - Grand Opening of the Vernor Building (Box 188)
        - Bill Signing Ceremony -- Immigrant Clerical Assistant Regulations (Box 188)
        - Ann Arbor Economic Dinner Club (Box 188)
        - Michigan Health and Hospital Association Annual Meeting (Box 188)
        - Millie Jeffery Remarks (Box 188)
        - Dawn Foods Products Ribbon Cutting Ceremony (Box 188)
        - Schakowsky for Congress Speech (Box 188)
        - Pfizer Announcements (Box 188)
        - Grand Traverse Democrats Breakfast (Box 188)
        - Farmland and Open Space Preservation Luncheon (Box 188)
        - Walter Legacy Act Pledge (Box 188)
        - Metropolitan, Organizing, Strategy, Enabling, Strength (MOSES) Meeting (Box 188)
        - Haworth Michigan Economic Growth Authority (MEGA) Announcement (Box 188)
        - Highland Park Demolition (Box 188)
        - National Urban League Conference (Box 188)
        - Parole Policy Press Conference (Box 188)
        - Pistons Trophy Display 2004 (Box 188)
        - Brown Trout Festival -- Ladies Classic Weigh-In (Box 188)
        - Ionia Free Fair Opening -- Governor’s Day Luncheon (Box 188)
        - Michigan Army National Guard Annual Review and Memorial Service (Box 188)
        - Center for Automotive Research (Box 188)
        - Byrnes Speech (Box 188)
        - Shabbat Unplugged (Box 188)
        - Speech for Graduation Ceremony for the Michigan Youth Challenge Academy (Box 188)
        - Electoral College Event (Box 188)
        - Family Independence Agency (FIA) Statewide Directors Meeting Awards Presentation (Box 188)
        - Commission on Higher Education and Economic Growth Report (Box 188)
        - Flint, GM Job Investment (Box 188)
        - Dedication of Riverwalk at Renaissance Center (Box 188)
        - “Operation Troop Connect” (Box 188)
        - Lead Bills Signing Event (Box 188)
        - “Tipping to Cool” Conference, Michigan Council for Arts and Cultural Affairs (MCACA) (Box 188)
        - FY 2005 Budget Letter (Box 188)
        - New State Employee Orientation (Box 188)
        - Habitat for Humanity (Box 188)
        - House District 85 Event (Box 188)
        - Owosso Rotary (Box 188)
        - House District 31 Event (Box 188)
        - Athletes with Disabilities Hall of Fame/Induction Ceremony (Box 188)
        - Washtenaw County Events (Box 188)
        - Flushing Education Forum (Box 188)
        - Gateway Dedication -- Veterans’ Ceremony (Box 188)
        - Yeshiva Beth Yehuda Annual Dinner (Box 188)
        - Rockford Education Forum (Box 188)
        - Madison Heights Education Forum (Box 188)
        - Press Event for Marie Donigan (Box 188)
        - Hino Motor Sales U.S.A. (Box 188)
        - Arab American PAC (Box 188)
        - Michigan Technological University YES! Expo (Box 188)
        - Eyes for Christmas (Box 188)
        - Return of the Guardian Building, 2 folders (Box 188)
        - Youth Education Summit “Every Child Can Succeed, No Exceptions, No Excuses” (Box 188)
        - Byrnes Institute (Box 188)
        - Battle Creek Chamber of Commerce (Box 188)
        - Radio Address (Box 188)
        - Water Legacy Act Meeting in Fenton (Box 188)
        - Mackinac Bridge Walk (Box 188)
        - Canadian Trash Event (Box 188)
        - Consular Corps Reception (Box 188)
        - Council of Economic Advisors (Box 188)
        - Governor’s Education Summit (Box 188)
        - Governor’s Education Summit Speech (Box 188)
        - Ryder Cup Match (Site Consultants Outreach) (Box 188)
        - Michigan Humanities Council’s 30th Anniversary (Box 188)
        - Ford Motor Company, Diversity Forum (Box 188)
        - Michigan Prescription Drug Card Rollout (Box 188)
        - Metropolitan, Organizing, Strategy, Enabling, Strength (MOSES) Public Meeting (Box 188)
        - Cherry Commission on Education and Economic Development-Lieutenant Governor’s Commission on Higher Education & Economic Development (Box 188)
        - Cherry Commission Meeting (Box 188)
        - Jobs and the Economy (Box 188)
        - American Bar Association (Box 188)
        - Joe Dumars Field House (Box 188)
        - Dow Corning Compound Semiconductor Solution Ribbon Cutting (Box 188)
        - Michigan National Guard Homecoming (Box 188)
        - Macomb County Faith and Community Leaders (Box 188)
        - Macomb County Ministerial Alliance & NAACP Symposium (Box 188)
        - Governor’s Interstate Indian Council (Box 189)
        - Michigan State Fair State Fairgrounds -- Detroit (Box 189)
        - Detroit Wayne County Health Authority 1st Meeting (Box 189)
        - National Speakers Conference (Box 189)
        - Governor’s Luncheon -- Upper Peninsula State Fair (Box 189)
        - Media Avail on Streamlined Permitting (Box 189)
        - Welcome Back Breakfast -- Novi Schools (Box 189)
        - Michigan Timely Application and Permit Service (MiTAPS) -- Directors Takai, Chester, and D. Hollister (Box 189)
        - Welcome Back Breakfast -- Port Huron Area School District (Box 189)
        - Dodge Dakota/Jeep Grand Cherokee (Box 189)
        - John Espinoza Trash Event (Box 189)
        - House Democrats’ Education Agenda with Marie Donigan (Box 189)
        - His Royal Highness Crown Prince of Jordan (Box 189)
        - Prescription Drug Press Event (Box 189)
        - Revolutionary Women Event (Box 189)
        - Sulfide Mining Bill Signing (Box 189)
        - Presentation from Lottery -- Press Availability (Box 189)
        - Michigan Women’s Hall of Fame Induction Remarks (Box 189)
        - Consular Corps Reception Remarks (Box 189)
      - 2005
        - Capitol Area Cesar E. Chavez Event (Box 189)
        - Detroit Economic Club (Box 189)
        - Habitat for Humanity Awards Dinner (Box 189)